var mercas = [ {question : "How many ternary sequences of length 8 do we have?",  answer : "balls - 8, the number of positions in the sequence urns - 3, is a 0, “is a 1”, and is a 2 3 8 = 6561"} , 
              {question : "How many ways to give 4 fruits (apple, orange,pear, and banana) to 11 people such that each receives one fruit, leaving 7 without a fruit?",  answer : "balls - 4, the fruits to give urns - 11, the different people, 7920"} ,
              {question : "An urn has balls numbered 0 to 9. Construct 3-digit lock code by extracting balls from the urn (first for the hundreds digit, second for the tens, third for the ones). How many possibilities are there (no number occurs twice)?",  answer : "balls - 3, the possible digits of the lock urns - 10, the different numbered balls, 720"} ,
              {question : "How many ways can 4 students from a group of 15 be lined up for a photograph?",  answer : "balls - 4, the number of photo slots urns - 15, the total number of students, 32760"} ,
              {question : "Lottery: chose five numbers from fifty.",  answer : "balls - 5, the number of extracted elements urns - 50, the possible values of the balls, 2118760"} ,
              {question : "How many ways of drawing six cards from a deck (52)?",  answer : "balls - 6, the number of cards to draw urns - 52, 52C6 = 20358520 "} ,
              {question : "How many ways of potting 3 balls in pool (16)?",  answer : "balls - 3, the number of balls to pot urns - 16, 16C3 = 560"} ,
              {question : "1 In how many ways can you distribute 16 oranges to five of your acquaintances?",  answer : "balls - 5, the length of the word urns - 26, the total number of letters, 30C5 = 142506"} ,
              {question : "In how many ways can you distribute 16 oranges to five of your friends (do not upset your friends – at least one each)?",  answer : "balls - 16, the total sum urns - 5, the different numbers to add, 15C11 = 1365"} ,
              {question : "Find the number of positive integer solutions of the equation x + y + z = 24", answer :"balls - 24, the total sum urns - 3, the 3 variables, 23C2 = 253"}
              {question : "How many ways are there to choose a 5-letter word from the 26-letter English alphabet, where words that are anagrams are considered the same, and every letter is used at least once?", answer :"balls - 5, the length of the word urns - 26, the total number of letters, 0 less balls than urns"}
              {question : "1 In how many ways can we partition a set of 3 elements into 2 non-empty sets?", answer :"S(3,2)=3"}
              {question : "In how many ways can the 10 students in a module be distributed to collaborate in 4 work groups?", answer :"balls - 10, the number of students urns - 4, number of work groups, 34105"}
              {question : "How many ways are there to distribute the 10 presents you have to the 6 members of your family?", answer :"balls - 10, the number of presents urns - 6, the different family members, 6!×S(10, 6)=6!×22,827 , 16435440  "}
              {question : "In how many ways can we create all sequences of length 8 that contain all of the letters {a, b, c, d}?", answer :"balls - 8, the number of positions urns - 4, the different letters, 4!×S(8, 4)=4!×1701 = 40824"}
              {question : "In how many ways can 5 final year projects be allocated to 9 different students (all projects must be allocated and some students might work in groups)!", answer :"balls - 9, the number of students urns - 5, the final year projects, 5!×S(9, 5)=5!×6951"}
              {question : "How many ways are there to distribute 10 pounds to 3 of your colleagues?", answer :"balls - 10, the money urns - 3, the different colleagues, sigma3 i=1 S(10, i)= S(10, 1)+ +S(10, 2)+S(10, 3)"}
              {question : "Consider all sequences of certain length. We say that two sequences are letter-equivalent, if we can obtain one from the other by a one-to-one letter substitution (aab is equivalent to both bba and ccb). How many letter-equivalent sequences of length three are there?", answer :"balls - 3, the length of the sequence urns - 3, the number of distinct letters, B3 = S(3, 1) + S(3, 2) + S(3, 3) = 1 + 3 + 1 = 5"}
              {question : "Fly Air is an airline that does not allocate flight seats (first come, first serve). In how many way can they sell tickets to 120 people.", answer :"balls - 120, the number of passengers urns - X, the number of seats, therefor is 1 if and only if urns > balls"}
              {question : "In how many ways can 120 students be fed pizza in a hall (none should starve, nor get more than one slice)?", answer :"balls - 120, the number of students urns - X, the number of pizza slices, 117 pizza slices - 0 ways / you kill students 200 pizza slices - 1 way 120 pizza slices - 1 way"}
              {question : "In how many ways can you place your 12 boules p´etanque set in your new bag?", answer :"balls - 12, number of boules urns - X, boules places in the bag, 14 places - 1 way 8 places - 0 ways / no brag points 11 places - 0 ways"}
              {question : "How can you fit 24 pigeons in their new lovely tree house?", answer :"balls - 24, the pigeons urns - X, the number of tree holes, 20 holes - 0 ways 28 holes - 1 way 24 holes - 1 way"}
              {question : "In how many ways can we decompose 8 into sums of 3 positive integers?", answer :""}
              {question : "In how many ways can we place ten oranges into five bags?", answer :"balls - 10, the number of oranges urns - 5, the number of bags, P5 i=1 pi(10)=1+5+8+9+7=30"}
              {question : "In how many ways can you hang eight shirts on four hangers?", answer :"balls - 8, the number of shirts urns - 4, the number of hangers, P4 i=1 pi(8)=1+4+5+5=15"}
              {question : "In how many ways can you visit in fifteen weeks twenty cities?", answer :"balls - 20, the number of cities urns - 15, the number of weeks, X15i=1pi(20) = 615"}
              {question : "you want to assinate robert mercas using 3 shots to make sure he is truely dead for being a bit of a cunt sometimes, you can choose from 6 body parts(head,chest etc..), how many different deaths of mercas are there?", answer :"6C3 = 20"}
             ];
var temp = Math.floor((Math.random() * mercas.length));
alert(mercas[temp].question);
alert(mercas[temp].answer);
